ARCHIE BATTLEY

SKILLSET

3D Modelling & Texturing, Blender, Maya, Zbrush, Forger, Nomad & Reality Capture

Concepting and 2D illustration

Brandina & Web Design. Adobe Creative Suite, Photoshop, Illustrator, HTML, CSS, React.js, Three.js, Bootstrap 4

STRENGTHS

Creative spirit Interpersonal skills Strong client relations Reliability Focus

REFERENCES

Ross Bowdler, Director Racecar New Media Services M: 07776133268 E:Ross@racecar.com

Sam Roe. Lecturer. UAL E:s.roe@lcc.arts.ac.uk

CONTACT

M: 07925 723711 E: archie@archiebattley.com W: <u>www.archiebattley.com</u> LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/archiebattley-7bb058221

PROFILE

I am a 3D Generalist and alumni from University of the Arts London, having received a First Class BA (Hons) Degree in 3D Computer Animation in 2023. I am extremely keen to start a career as a 3D Artist in a junior/graduate position in the creative industry.

I have over 8 years experience in using Adobe Creative Suite applications for design and video applications. I am also experienced with HTML, CSS and JS from my time as a web designer.

I have utilised a wide range of 3D & 2D production software during my studies as well as in my freelance professional career, including but not limited to: Maya, Blender, Substance 3D Painter, ZBrush, Marvelous Designer, Unreal Engine, Reality Capture & Quixel Bridge. I have been able to use these skills on my personal work, a collaborative music video project with my peers as well as in my current freelance projects.

Here is a link to my portfolio website <u>www.archiebattley.com</u> where you will see my showreel and a selection of my projects.

WORK HISTORY

Racecar New Media Services - Sep 2020 - Now

FREELANCE 3D ARTIST / PHOTOGRAPHER / VIDEO EDITOR

- Creating optimised 3D Assets for use on web view integrations. (From ideation to subdivision modelling & texturing)
- Developing an integrated high-performance product configurator with the google model viewer API JavaScript library
- Filming, Editing & Video Production of interviews
- Photography & Video for automotive & marine clients: Talacrest Classic Ferrari, Mission Prestige, Neil Bainbridge Engineering & Broadblue Catamarans

Racecar New Media Services - Shere, Surrey - June 2015 - Sep 2020

FRONTEND DEVELOPER AND VIDEO PRODUCTION ASSISTANT

- HTML and CSS Development for Webpage Styling and Responsive Content Presentation using Frameworks: Bootstrap 4 and React.js
- Website Graphics Design and Production for the Automotive Industry. Content management for mail campaigns and website stock editors.
- Film Editing/Video Production
- Improving Brand Identities and Social Media Presence for Clients
- Bespoke photography for classic automotive clients such as: Tim Samways Sporting & Historic Car Engineers, Shapecraft Classic Motor Bodies

VOLUNTARY WORK EXPERIENCE

Target3D - Tower Hamlets, London - July 2023

MOTION CAPTURE RUNNER (DAY WORK EXPERIENCE)

- Assisting in Preparing Props for Motion Capture Using Markers
- Volume & Filming Reference Footage

Creative Assembly - Horsham, West Sussex - June 2023

CONSOLE 3D ART DEPARTMENT SHADOW (DAY WORK EXPERIENCE)

- Shadowing the 3D Art Department Team Leads
- · Learning About Edge Flow and Topology
- Calibrating Props for Use in Motion Capture Taught about subdivision modelling in Blender
- Providing Assistance to Talent in the Mocap Reporting to the UK Secretary of State for Culture, Media and Sport

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS, 3D COMPUTER ANIMATION

University of the Arts London, London College of Communication 2020 - 2023 First Class Honours

Godalming College 2016 - 2018 Level 3 BTEC. ICT A Level Graphic Design A Level Geography